If everybody says this is going to be very tough, I'm very interested in that tough question.
And I pick up and say how can we do it in a different way?
Because nothing is easy. Nothing is free.
If you want to be successful, you have to think different.
You have to do different. You have to pay the price.
I'll leave up by 18 years to today's size.
Yeah, we are lucky. But we work much harder than most of the people.
We never sleep well and sound in the evening.
I struggled last year 867 hours a year in the flip lane.
In the plane. I'm working hard. My team working very hard.
18 years, we work like a normal company.
70 years. Day and night. Nothing is free.
Nothing is easy.